You've got to start at the bottom before you take it from the top.
The High Note is a romance, comedy, music film directed by Nisha Ganatra.
Set in the dazzling world of the LA music scene comes the story of Grace Davis, a
superstar whose talent, and ego, have reached unbelievable heights.
Maggie is Grace’s overworked personal assistant who’s stuck running errands, but
still aspires to her childhood dream of becoming a music producer.
When Grace’s manager presents her with a choice that could alter the course of her career,
Maggie and Grace come up with a plan that could change their lives forever.
Maggie Sherwoode, played by Dakota Johnson.
Grace Davis, played by Tracee Ellis Ross.
Jack Robertson, played by Ice Cube.
David Cliff, played by Kelvin Harrison, Jr..
Max, played by Bill Pullman.
Gail, played by June Diane Raphael.
The High Note is a 2020 American comedy-drama film directed by
Nisha Ganatra and written by Flora Greeson.
It stars Dakota Johnson, Tracee Ellis Ross, Kelvin Harrison Jr., Zoë Chao, Bill Pullman, Eddie Izzard, and Ice
Cube, and follows a famous singer's personal assistant who wants to become a music producer.
The film was released in select theaters and through premium video on demand
(PVOD) in the United States on May 29, 2020, by Focus Features.
It received mixed reviews from critics, although the cast was praised.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.